<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<title>pages tagged random</title>
<link href="http://io/~zlatan/Minorbits/tags/random/"/>
<link href="http://io/~zlatan/Minorbits/tags/random/index.atom" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
<author>

<name>Minor bits</name>

</author>




<id>http://io/~zlatan/Minorbits/tags/random/</id>

<subtitle type="html">Minor bits</subtitle>
<generator uri="http://ikiwiki.info/">ikiwiki</generator>
<updated>2014-02-14T15:24:23Z</updated>
<entry>
	<title>Random bits</title>

	<id>http://io/~zlatan/Minorbits/posts/Random_bits/</id>

	<link href="http://io/~zlatan/Minorbits/posts/Random_bits/"/>






	<category term="bits" />

	<category term="random" />


	<updated>2014-02-14T15:24:23Z</updated>
	<published>2014-02-14T15:22:33Z</published>


	<content type="html" xml:lang="en">
	&lt;p&gt;This are mine &lt;em&gt;random&lt;/em&gt; bits for my first posting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Debian &lt;a href=&quot;http://qa.debian.org/developer.php?login=zlatan.todoric%40gmail.com&quot;&gt;QA page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;* Randomness&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Debian&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;A sociologist, a psychologist, and a engineer were discussing the
consequences and implications of a married man&#39;s having a mistress.  The
sociologist&#39;s opinion was that it is absolutely and categorically unforgivable
for a married man to forfeit the bond of matrimony, and engage in such lowly
and lustful pursuits.
    The psychologist&#39;s opinion was that although morally reprehensible,
if a man MUST have a mistress to achieve his full potential as a human being,
then -- well -- he may go ahead and choose to have a mistress, as long as he
is considerate enough to keep this secret from his wife.
    The engineer then interjected: &quot;I also believe that, if necessary,
a married man is entitled to a mistress.  However, I do not see why the
affair should be concealed from the wife.  On the contrary, if the affair
is out in the open, then on Friday evenings he may tell his wife that he
is going to see his mistress, tell his mistress that he is going to be with
his wife, then go to his office and get some work done!&quot;
&lt;/pre&gt;




	</content>



</entry>

</feed>
